EVERETT HANDY

MARKETING & SALES PROFESSIONAL

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Marketing and Sales Representative with five years of experience –current MBA student at UNC Charlotte focused on Marketing. Excellent interpersonal communication and team skills. Listens attentively, communicates persuasively and follows through diligently. Persuasive communicator and analytical problem solver skilled in uncovering customer needs and matching with company offerings.

EXPERIENCE

SALES AND MARKETING MANAGER

Polyprint USA. Charlotte, NC

Sep. 2021 - Oct. 2022

- Implemented sales and marketing strategies for Direct-to-Garment printers and product launches in North American markets.
- Evaluated and advised Sales and Marketing teams to improve revenue, retention, and marketing metrics.
- Recruited, mentored, and supervised new employees to exceed sales and marketing expectations.
- Proficient with HubSpot CRM to analyze, forecast, and improve sales KPIs and metrics.

PATIENT SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Equiscript, LLC. North Charleston, SC

Jan. 2021 - Sep. 2021

- Enrolled Patients for Non-profit Health Centers and Pharmacies.
- Used Salesforce CRM to generate new enrollments and maintain detailed contact logs and account records of prospective clients, their medications and insurance records.
- Maintained HIPPA compliance and quality assurance while representing Equiscript and their 340B health center clients.

DIGITAL MARKETING & SALES REPRESENTATIVE

Townsquare Interactive. Charlotte, NC

Oct. 2018 - Dec. 2020

- Demonstrated Digital Marketing strategies based on customer needs. Managed customers' websites, SEO and social media.
- Used CRMs to generate sales leads and maintain detailed contact logs and account records of prospective customers and clients.
- Excelled in full-cycle sales. Prospected potential customers presented our SaaS persuasively and onboarded new clients.
- Followed up with customers after completed sales to assess satisfaction and resolve any technical or service concerns.

- everettdhandy@outlook.com
- 704 517 5606
- Charlotte, NC 28202

SKILLS

- Verbal and written communication
- Public Speaking and Sales Presentations
- Digital and Social Media Marketing
- Advanced Salesforce and HubSpot CRM User
- New Customer Acquisition and Sales
- Client Retention and Account Management

EDUCATION

Master of Business Administration (MBA), Marketing

Enrolled at the University of North Carolina at Charlotte

- Expected graduation
 Dec. 2023
- Current GPA: 4.0

Bachelor of Arts in English and Communication, Double Major

University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill

- Graduated May 2017 with 3.34 GPA
- Communication focus in Rhetorical Studies.